Guide to the South Asian Pamphlets Collection, 1920-2005 (bulk 1950-2000) RL.01235
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- India Pamphlets, 1920-2005, bulk 1960-1990, 177 boxes
  - Political Parties, 1961-1990, 15 Boxes
    - Political Parties, Miscellaneous Titles, 1952-1990, 2 boxes
      - Land Reforms and Call for Action. Surjeet, Harkishan Singh. Delhi, All India Kisan Sabha, India: 1989. (Box IN-127)
      - Manifesto of the Left Front. West Bengal Left Front Committee. Calcutta, India: 1982. (Box IN-127)
        West Bengal Assembly Elections (1982).
      - National Front: Lok Sabha Elections 1989 Manifesto. National Front. New Delhi, India: 1989. (Box IN-127)
      - 1974 Election Manifesto. Nagaland Nationalist Organisation. Kohima, India: 1974. (Box IN-127)
      - People's Liberation: Characteristics of Parties, Movements and People's Struggles in India. Lourdusamy, Stan. New Delhi, Indian Social Institute, India: 1985. (Box IN-128)
        Monograph Series No. 24.
      - Policy Statement. Democratic Socialist Party. New Delhi, India: 1978? (Box IN-128)
      - Praja Socialism: Monopoly's Pawn. Narayanan, Edatata. Bombay, People's Publishing House Limited, India: 1952. (Box IN-128)
      - Report Presented By B.D. Khobragade, General Secretary of Republican Party of India. Republican Party of India. New Delhi, India: 1966. (Box IN-128)
      - Republican Party Of India: Resolutions Passed in the 5th Conference of the Republican Party of India Held at New Delhi on the 1st May, 1966. Republican Party of India. New Delhi, India: 1966. (Box IN-128)
      - Resolutions. All India Hindu Convention. New Delhi, India: 196-? (Box IN-128)
      - Resolutions Adopted by the AIKC of the All India Kisan Sabha, New Delhi, 27-28 October 1967. All India Kisan Sabha. New Delhi, India: 1967. (Box IN-128)
      - Shiv Sena Phenomenon, The. Gangadharan, K. K., and Gogate, Sudha. New Delhi, India: 197-? (Box IN-128)
      - Socialist Alternative, A. Praja Socialist Party. Lucknow, India: 1967. (Box IN-128)
        Text of the Election Manifesto Adopted by the General Council of the Praja Socialist Party at its meeting held at Lucknow from October 7-9, 1966.
      - Sonepur Special Convention: Resolution and Documents. Samyukta Socialist Party. New Delhi, India: 1970. (Box IN-128)
      - Speech by B.K.Gaikwad, President, Republican Party of India. Republican Party of India. New Delhi, India: 1966. (Box IN-128)
      - Statement of Policy. Praja Socialist Party. Bombay, India: 1954. (Box IN-128)
      - Strategy for Socialism. Praja Socialist Party. Bombay, India: 1970. (Box IN-128)
      - Towards a Pro-Rural Poor Agrarian Policy. All India Kisan Sabha. New Delhi, India: 1990. (Box IN-128)
        Proceedings, General Secretary's Report, Resolutions and Concluding Speech by Com. H. S. Surjeet at CKC/AIKC Meeting, Patna, Bihar, 17-19 August 1990.
      - Towards All India Action Programme. All India Kisan Sabha. New Delhi, India: 1987. (Box IN-128)
        Proceedings, General Secretary's Report and Resolutions of the CKC & AIKC Meetings, Cuttack (Orissa), 24-26 April, 1987.
      - Towards Country-Wide Peasant Struggles. All India Kisan Sabha. New Delhi, India: 1986. (Box IN-128)
        Proceedings, Resolutions, General Secretary's Report, and Statement of Policy as Approved by the Thane Meeting of the Central Kisan Committee of the All India Kisan Sabha, held on September 26-28, 1986.
      - Towards Socialist Transformation. Praja Socialist Party. Bombay, India: 1971. (Box IN-128)
      - Two Years of the Praja Socialist Party. Praja Socialist Party. Bombay, India: 1954. (Box IN-128)
      - What the AIKS Stands For. Singh, Harkishan SurjeetNew Delhi, All India Kisan Sabha, India: 1986. (Box IN-128)
        1936-1986 Golden Jubilee Series no. 8.
      - Why Praja Socialist? Goray, N. G., and Dwivedy, Surendranath. Bombay, Popular Prakashan, India: 196-? (Box IN-128)
      - Why Samyukta Socialist? Limaye, Madhu. Bombay, Popular Prakashan, India: 196-? (Box IN-128)
      - Your Man for the Lok Sabha: Brij Mohan Toofan, P.S.P. Candidate for New Delhi Constituency. Praja Socialist Party. New Delhi, India: 196-? (Box IN-128)
    - Swatantra Party, 1959-1971, 1 box
      - Conference Committee Chairman's Address. Nanda, H. P. New Delhi, Swatantra Party, India: 1966. (Box IN-129)
        Speech given on first day of Fourth National Convention held on Dec. 12 & 13, 1966.
      - Constitution. Swatantra Party. Bombay, India: 1968. (Box IN-129)
        As amended on October 5, 1968 by the Fifth National Convention in Bhubaneswar.
      - Constitution (Twentyfourth) Amendment Bill, The. Swatantra Party. Bombay, India: 1971. (Box IN-129)
        Swatantra Party General Council held at Bangalore, Sept. 17-18, 1971.
      - Co-Operation or Coercion? Swatantra Party. Bombay, India: 1960? (Box IN-129)
        Swatantra Public Education Series - 2.
      - Election Manifesto. Swatantra Party. Bombay, India: 196-? (Box IN-129)
      - Fundamental Rights: Our Protection Against Tyranny. Meghrajji, Sriraj. Bombay, Swatantra Party, India: 196-? (Box IN-129)
        For This We Stand - XII.
      - Inaugural Speech. Rajagopalachari, C. Delhi, Swatantra Party, India: 1966. (Box IN-129)
        Speech given on Monday, December 12, 166 at the National Convention held at Delhi.
      - Lessons of the Bengal Crisis and What Next? Masani, M. R., and Dandeker, N. Bombay, Swatantra Party, India: 1968. (Box IN-129)
        The first and second essays have been written by the first and second authors, respectively.
      - Lokpal Bill, 1967, The. Deo, P. K. Bombay, Swatantra Party, India: 1967? (Box IN-129)
      - Mid-Term Report. Swatantra Party. Bombay, India: 1969. (Box IN-129)
        Adopted by the General Council of the Swatantra Party on November 15-16, 1969.
      - National Executive Resolutions. Swatantra Party. Bombay, India: 1965. (Box IN-129)
        Held at New Delhi, Nov. 1 and 2, 1965.
      - National Priorities for 1970. Masani, M. R. Bombay, Swatantra Party, India: 1969. (Box IN-129)
        Transcript of a press conference addressed by the author in New Delhi on 31 December 1969.
      - Our Foreign Policy: A Plea for Realism. Masani, M. R. Bombay, Swatantra Party, India: 1965. (Box IN-129)
        Resolution of the National Executive of the Swatantra Party, November 2, 1965.
      - People Are Sovereign, The. Mody, Piloo. Bombay, Swatantra Party, India: 1967. (Box IN-129)
        Based on a speech in the Lok Sabha delivered in two parts on June 23 and July 7, 1967 during the discussion on Mr. Nath Pai's Constitution Amendment Bill.
      - Preparedness for Defence. Dandeker, N. Bombay, Swatantra Party, India: 1967. (Box IN-129)
        For This We Stand - VIII, based on speech delivered in the Lok Sabha on June 26, 1967 during a debate on the Demand for Grants to the Ministry of Defence.
      - Presidential Address. Ranga, N. G. Bombay, Swatantra Party, India: 1966. (Box IN-129)
        Given at the Fourth National Convention, New Delhi, December 12 & 13, 1966.
      - Rising Star, The. Swatantra Party, Bombay. Bombay, India: 197-? (Box IN-129)
      - Social and Religious Decay. Rajagopalachari, C. Bombay, Swatantra Party, India: 196-? (Box IN-129)
      - Socialism: An Ism That Has Become a Wasm. Swatantra Party. Bombay, India: 196-? (Box IN-129)
        Swatantra Public Education Series - 1.
      - Statement of Principles. Swatantra Party. Bombay, India: 1959. (Box IN-129)
        Adopted at the Preparatory Convention held at Bombay on August 1 and 2, 1959.
      - Statism Rejected: Ceylon Shows the Way. Swatantra Party. Bombay, India: 1964? (Box IN-129)
      - Structure of Party Organisation. Swatantra Party. Bombay, India: 1969. (Box IN-129)
        Swatantra Organisation Series: No. 1.
      - Swatantra Alternative to Third Plan. Ranga, N. G., and Masani, M. R. Bombay, Swatantra Party, India: 1963. (Box IN-129)
        From their speeches in Parliament.
      - Swatantra Party General Council, Souvenir. Swatantra Party. Bombay, India: 1971. (Box IN-129)
        Held at Baroda, 6th Nov. 1971.
      - Swatantra Speaks to the Poor. Swatantra Party. Bombay, India: 1965? (Box IN-129)
        For This We Stand: I.
      - This Poor Man Prefers Swatantra. Swatantra Party. Bombay, India: 196-? (Box IN-129)
        For This We Stand: II.
      - To Prosperity Through Freedom: The Swatantra Party's Statement of Policy. Swatantra Party. Bombay, India: 1960. (Box IN-129)
        Adopted at the National Convention in Patna on March 19 & 20, 1960.
      - Voice of the People, The. Masani, M. R., and Dandeker, N. Bombay, India: 1965. (Box IN-129)
      - We Accuse! Deo, P. K., and Dandeker, N. Bombay, India: 1965. (Box IN-129)
      - What's Wrong with the Third Plan? Swatantra Party. Bombay, India: 1960. (Box IN-129)
        Swatantra Series - 5.
      - Who is Outdated? Swatantra Party. Bombay, India: 1960? (Box IN-129)
      - Who is Outdated?: German Socialists Echo Swatantra. Swatantra Party. Bombay, India: 1960? (Box IN-129)
      - Who's to Hold That Price Line? Pai, M. R. Bombay, India: 1964? (Box IN-129)
      - Why I Took to Politics. Rai, Charanjit. Bombay, India: 1965. (Box IN-129)
      - Why Swatantra? Masani, M. R. Bombay, India: 196-? (Box IN-129)
      - Why Swatantra?: To Save Freedom…To Preserve Family Economy…To Restore Fundamental Rights…To Provide a Democratic Alternative. Swatantra Party. Bombay, India: 196-? (Box IN-129)
        Swantantra Series - 2.
      - Why Swatantra Supports Tashkent Agreement? Patel, Dahyabhai V., and Deo, P. K. Bombay, Swatantra Party, India: 1966. (Box IN-129)
        Text of speech delivered in the Lok Sabha on 16-2-66.
  - Politics and Government, 1928-1991, 8 boxes
    The 260 pamphlets in this large section were published by official government agencies, NGOs, political parties and individuals. They discuss such topics as economic development, administration, corruption in government, the Punjab problem, affirmative action, uplift of economically disadvantaged classes, the Punjab/Khalistan issue, political alliances among the various parties, civil service, views by extremist groups, center-state relations, and the Naxalite and the Telengana struggle. Formats include conference proceedings, lectures by various political personalities, and speeches and addresses by members of legislatures and governors.
    - Address by Dr. Shanker Dayal Sharma, President, Indian National Congress. Sharma, Shanker Dayal. New Delhi, All India Congress Committee, India: 1972. (Box IN-130)
      All India Congress Committee Meeting, Delhi June 1 & 2, 1972.
    - Address by Sri Bisnuram Medhi, Governor of Madras at the Joint Session of the Madras Legislature. Medhi, Bisnuram. Hyderabad, The Protection Line Publications, India: 1982. (Box IN-130)
      Publication No.14.
    - Address by Sri Pattom A. Thanu Pillai. Pillai, Pattom A. Thanu. Hyderabad, Govt. of Andra Pradesh, India: 1965. (Box IN-130)
    - Address Delivered by Shri A.K. Roy. Vidhan Sabha Secretariat, Chandigarh. Chandigarh, Punjab Vidhan Parishad Secretariat, India: 1966. (Box IN-130)
      Address delivered to The Public Accounts Committee of the Punjab Vidhan Sabha and the offices of the Govt.
    - Address of Shri Hiteswar Saikia, Chief Minister, Assam. Saikia, Hiteshwar. New Delhi, National Integration Council, India: 1984. (Box IN-130)
      In the meeting of National Integration Council, New Delhi.
    - AIBEA: The Hand-Maid of Communists. All India Bank Employees Association. Bangalore, Puranik, A.M., NOBW Publication, India: 1966. (Box IN-130)
    - All India League for Revolutionary Culture: Souvenir. New Delhi, All India League for Revolutionary Culture, India: 1983. (Box IN-130)
    - All-India Institute of Local Self-Government. All-India Institute of Local Self-Government. Bombay, Sthanikraj Bhavan, India: 1987. (Box IN-130)
      Proceedings and recommendations of the National Conference of Urban Bodies in India held in Bombay on September 26-27, 1986.
    - Anti- Betterment Levy Struggle of Punjab. Surjeet, Harkishan Singh. New Delhi, All India Kisan Sabha, India: 1986. (Box IN-130)
      1936-86 Golden Jubilee Series No.4.
    - Appeal to the Nation (Our Duty & Programme), An. Sarva Seva Sangh Prakashan. Varanasi, Sarva Seva Sangh Prakashan, India: 1982. (Box IN-130)
    - Are Solemn Pledges Scraps of Paper? Singh, Karni. Bikaner, [no publisher], India: 196-? (Box IN-130)
    - Arun Shourie. Shourie, Arun. Rohtak, Dept. of Journalism & Mass Communication, India: 1981. (Box IN-130)
      A study of his articles published in the Indian Express, New Delhi Edition, from Aug.1980 to Nov. 1980.
    - Assam Events in Perspective. India. Ministry of Information and Broadcasting. New Delhi, India: 1983. (Box IN-130)
    - Assault on Democratic Rights in Contemporary India. Desai, A. R. Bombay, C.G.Shah Memorial Trust Publication, India: 1985. (Box IN-130)
      What is behind the assault on Democratic rights ?
    - Assault on Parliamentary Democracy in Tripura. Communist Party of India (Marxist), Tripura State Committee. New Delhi, Communist Party of India (Marxist) Tripura State Committee, India: 1988. (Box IN-130)
    - Back to Square One, Report on Punjab. Vajpayee, A. B., andBJP Study Team. New Delhi, India: 1988. (Box IN-130)
    - Balasaheb Deoras with Delhi Newsmen. Press Club of India. Delhi, Suruchi Sahitya, India: 1979. (Box IN-130)
      First Edition: 1979.
    - Balasaheb's Speech in Jamshedpur. Suruchi Sahitya. Delhi, Suruchi Sahitya, India: 1981. (Box IN-130)
      English rendering of the tape-recorded speech delivered in Hindi on 1-4-1979 which in the eyes of the Jitendra Narayan Commission is a 'Communal Propaganda'.
    - Big Business under Congress Raj. Roy, Ajit. New Delhi, Communist Party of India, India: 1961. (Box IN-130)
    - Birth Pangs of Khalistan, The. Dalit Sahitya Akademy, Bangalore. Bangalore, Dalit Sahitya Akademy, India: 1985. (Box IN-130)
    - Blue Print for a National Alternative. Madhok, Balraj. New Delhi, Bharatiya Jansangh Publication, India: 1984. (Box IN-130)
    - Brochure on Mobility of Personnel Between Central Government and Central Autonomous Bodies… India. Ministry of Personnel, Public Grievancances and Pensions. Delhi, Controller of Publications, India: 1987. (Box IN-130)
    - Call of Bharat, The. Rao, K. G. Babu. Machilipatnam, Andhra, India: 1966. (Box IN-130)
    - Case of Bharatiya Jana Sangh, The. Punjab State Bharatiya Jana Sangh. Jullundur City, India: 196-? (Box IN-130)
      Memorandum. Submitted to the Parliament and Cabinet Committees to "find a cooperative solution to the demand of Punjabi Suba."
    - Centre-State Relations. Desai, A. R. [?], C. G. Shah Memorial Trust, India: 1978? (Box IN-130)
    - Centre State Relations. India. Publications Division. New Delhi, Govt. of India, India: 1967. (Box IN-130)
    - Centre State Relations. Ranadive, B. T. Delhi, Janavadi Vichar Manch, University of Delhi, India: 1978? (Box IN-130)
      (In the Indian Context, 1977- 1978).
    - Challenge in Punjab, The. A.I.C.C.(I) New Delhi, A.I.C.C.(I) Publication, India: 197-? (Box IN-130)
    - Charter of demands, The. Republican Party of India, The. Delhi, Republican Party of India, India: 1964. (Box IN-130)
      Submitted to: Shri Lal Bahadur Shastri.
    - Citizens for Democracy. Narayan, Jayaprakash. New Delhi, Janatantra Samaj, India: 198-? (Box IN-130)
      Purpose and Programme.
    - Communist Approach, The. Gour, Raj Bahadur. New Delhi, Communist Party Publication, India: 1969. (Box IN-130)
      Telengana Tangle.
    - Conference of Political Parties and Chief Ministers in Calcutta. Basu, Jyoti. Calcutta, Information And Cultural Affairs Dept., Govt. of West Bengal, India: 1984. (Box IN-130)
    - Congress Path to Communism, The. Masani, M. R. Bombay, People's Publishing House Ltd., India: 1952. (Box IN-130)
    - Conspiracy to Wreck W. Bengal United Front. Communist Party of India (Marxist). New Delhi, Communist Party of India (Marxist), India: 1970. (Box IN-130)
    - Constitution: A Curse to the Hindus. Joshi, P. N. New Delhi, Rashtraya Hindu Manch, India: 1990. (Box IN-130)
      Article 27 & 28 a Black Law.
    - Cooperation and Social Justice. Weeraman, P. E. New Delhi, Int'l Cooperative Alliance, Regional Office and Education Centre for South-East Asia, India: 1976. (Box IN-131)
      Cooperative Series; 20.
    - Corruption Charges Boomerang. Government of Kerala. Trivandrum, India: 1989. (Box IN-131)
    - Corruption in India, Ramifications and Remedies. Joshi, S. M. New Delhi, Jayaprakash Foundation, India: 1982. (Box IN-131)
      JP Memorial lecture 1981.
    - Council of Ministers: 1984-1987. Lok Sabha Secretariat, New Delhi. New Delhi, Lok Sabha Secretariat, India: 1988. (Box IN-131)
      Names & Portfolios of the Members of the Union Council of Ministers.
    - Country's Unity: A Must. Deoras, Bala Saheb. New Delhi, Suruchi Prakashan, India: 1985. (Box IN-131)
    - CPM Terror in West Bengal. Gupta, Bhupesh, and Sen, Ramen, and Gupta, Prabhat Das. New Delhi, Communist Party Publication, India: 1970. (Box IN-131)
    - Crisis of 1971, The. Aiya, S. V. C. New Delhi, National Council of Educational Research and Training, India: 1971. (Box IN-131)
    - Dangerous Octopus in the Indian Ocean. Moorthy, A. S. New Delhi, Kalamkar Prakashan Private Ltd., India: 1980. (Box IN-131)
      First Published: October 1980.
    - Dawn is Near, The. Gandhi, Indira. Delhi, Publications Division, India: 1967. (Box IN-131)
    - Decision of the Press Council is Unfortunate, The. De, Niren. [n.p.], [no publisher], India: 1970. (Box IN-131)
      There Has Been No Attempt to Appreciate the Point of View of Government.
    - Decisions From the Chair In the Assam Legislative Assembly. Research and Reference Section, Assam Legislative Assembly Secretariat, Dispur. Dispur, Research and Reference Section, Assam Legislative Assembly, India: 1973. (Box IN-131)
    - Defeat Separatist Conspiracy in Andhra. Rao, C. Rajeswara. New Delhi, Communist Party Publication, India: 1973. (Box IN-131)
    - Defence Minister, Shri Jagjivan Ram's Reply to the Debate on Budget Demands of the Ministry of Defence. India. Ministry of External Affairs. New Delhi, India: 1972. (Box IN-131)
    - Democracy and Cult of Individual. Kumaramangalam, Mohan. New Delhi, National Book Club, India: 1966. (Box IN-131)
    - Democracy on the Defensive. Mathur, A. B. Jodhpur, All India Political Science Association, India: 1981. (Box IN-131)
      Prof. G.D. Sondhi memorial lecture delivered at the 41st All India Political Science Conference held at Ranchi, through October 12-14, 1981.
    - Democratic Socialism. Jain, K. P. Agra, Sahitya Bhawan, India: 197-? (Box IN-131)
    - Devaluation: The Guilty Men. Swantantra Party, Bombay. Bombay, Swatantra Party Publication, India: 1966. (Box IN-131)
      For this we stand IV.
    - Developments in Punjab. Surjeet, Harkishan Singh. New Delhi, Communist Party Of India (Marxist), India: 1984. (Box IN-131)
    - Dictatorship for India. Naik, J. A. Kolhapur, [no publisher], India: 1985. (Box IN-131)
    - Dravidar Kazhagam, The: What It Stands For? The Dravidar Kazhagam.Madras, India: 1982. (Box IN-131)
    - Education and the National Emergency for Schools, Teachers and Pupils. National Council of Educational Research and Training. New Delhi, National Council of Educational Research and Training, India: 197-? (Box IN-131)
    - Eighth Conference of Commonwealth Speakers. Kashyap, Subhash C. New Delhi, Lok Sabha Secretariat, India: 1986. (Box IN-131)
      Monograph Series 7.
    - Emergence of Modern India, The: Retrospect and Prospect. Kumar, Ravinder. Shimla, Indian Institute of Advanced Study, India: 1990. (Box IN-131)
    - Emergency and the Communist Party. Rao, C. Rajeswara, and Gupta, Bhupesh, and Sen, Mohit. New Delhi, Communist Party Publication, India: 1975. (Box IN-131)
    - Emergency in India, The. Educational Resources Centre, New Delhi. New Delhi, Educational Resources Centre, India: 1977. (Box IN-131)
      News & Reviews from ERC. (No.12).
    - Emergency? Patel, Dahyabhai V. Bombay, [no publisher], India: 1963? (Box IN-131)
    - Essential Services Maintenance Ordinance - Why? A.I.C.C.(I)New Delhi, AICC(I), India: 1981. (Box IN-131)
      A.I.C.C. (I) Series 2.
    - Evaluation of a Pledge, An. West Bengal. Information and Cultural Affairs Dept. Calcutta, Govt. of West Bengal, India: 1980. (Box IN-131)
    - Expunctions From Parliament Proceedings. Lok Sabha Secretariat, New Delhi. New Delhi, Lok Sabha Secretariat, India: 1985. (Box IN-131)
    - Face of Megalomania, The. [Ganesh]. New Delhi, All India Congress Committee, India: 197-? (Box IN-132)
    - Fair Deal for Public Servants, A. Dandekar, N. Bombay, Committee of Independent Trade Unions, India: 1964. (Box IN-132)
    - First Report of the Ninth Finance Commission: Prejudicial and Discriminating. Govt. of Kerala. Trivandrum, India: 199-? (Box IN-132)
    - First Six months of Left Front Ministry in West Bengal. West Bengal. Dept. of Information & Public Relations. Calcutta, India: 1982? (Box IN-132)
    - First Year of Statehood: Himachal Pradesh. Himachal Pradesh. Director Public Relations. Simla, India: 1973? (Box IN-132)
    - For a Prosperous Tomorrow. Anonymous. Delhi, [no publisher], India: 197-? (Box IN-132)
      Issued by candidates opposed to Congress Party (I). Includes a list of the candidates.
    - "For God's Sake, Go". Masani, M. R. Bombay, Swatantra Party Publication, India: 1966? (Box IN-132)
      For this we stand- VI.
    - Four Pillar State: An Outline. Limaye, Madhu. Bombay, Parikh, G.G., India: 1973. (Box IN-132)
    - Free and Balanced Press, A. Venkataramiah, E. S. New Delhi, TRF Institute for Social Sciences, India: 1986. (Box IN-132)
    - Gandhi, Gorbachev and India Today. Sardesai, S. G. New Delhi, Perspective Publications (P) Ltd., India: 198-? (Box IN-132)
    - Gandhism. Ambedkar, B. R. Jalandhar, Buddhist Publishing house, India: 1945. (Box IN-132)
      A reprint of chapter 'Gandhism' from Dr. Ambedkar's book WHAT CONGRESS AND GANDHI HAVE DONE TO THE UNTOUCHABLES.
    - Gorbachevism, Art Systems of Russia and India and a Hundred Flowers of Compradoriam. Purohit, Vinayak. Bombay, Indian Institute of Social Research, India: 1989. (Box IN-132)
      With a note on Deng's China.
    - Gorkhaland Agitation: A Part of Imperialist Plot in the East. Ranadive, B. T. Calcutta, West Bengal State Committee, Communist Party of India (Marxist), India: 1986. (Box IN-132)
    - Govern or Get Out. India. Delhi, Sharma, Krishna Lal, India: 1984. (Box IN-132)
      A Report On N.D.A. Satyagraha in Delji From May 3 to 9, 1984.
    - Governors: To Be or Not to Be. To Reign Not To Rule. Iyer, V. R. Krishna. Delhi, All India Lawyers Union, India: 1989. (Box IN-132)
      All India lawyers Union Convention on Governors, April 8, 1989.
    - Great Task Before Us, The. Shastri, Lal BahadurDirectorate of Advertising and Visual Publicity, Ministry of I. and B., Government of IndiaIndia: 1964. (Box IN-132)
    - Guide to Parliament House. Lok Sabha Secretariat, New Delhi. New Delhi, Lok Sabha Secretariat, India: 1968. (Box IN-132)
    - Guidelines for People's Committees. Desai, Narayan, ed. Varanasi, Sarva-Seva-Sangh-Prakashan, India: 1978. (Box IN-132)
      On the movement started by Jai Prakash Narain in 1977; articles.
    - Hail, Revolution! All India League For Revolutionary Culture. Delhi, Progressive Publishers, India: 1983. (Box IN-132)
      Publication No.1.
    - Haryana: Towards a Welfare State. Public Relations Department, Haryana. Haryana, India: 1969? (Box IN-132)
      Nation Building Activities of the State Government. At a Glance: 1968-69.
    - Hill Areas of Assam under the Leadership of Youths. Guwahati, Janasanyog (Hills), India: 1988. (Box IN-132)